GABRIEL RUIZ MUÑOZ

Developer

Address.

2 Fumistería street, 28037, Madrid, Spain

Phone number. (+34) 644 466 698 Email.

gabriel.rmunoz.developer@tutanota.com



ABOUT ME

Higher Technician in Multiplatform Application Development and developer with more than three years of experience with Java and PL/SQL for back-end and HTML, CSS and JavaScript for front-end.

Development of projects through the use of frameworks such as Struts and Spring. Responsible for the development and testing of improvements with JUnit library. Familiar with the use of AGILE methodologies, more specifically with SCRUM. You can know me a little more at: https://gabrielrmunoz.github.io/AboutMe/

EDUCATION

Sep. 2013 - Jul. 2016

I.E.S. LÁZARO CÁRDENAS

High-Level Technical Degree in Multi-platform Applications Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov. 2018 - Sep. 2019

RECREATIVOS FRANCO DIGITAL - Back-end developer

Java - JUnit - Gradle - CVS

May. 2018 - Nov. 2018

WORLDLINE GLOBAL - Full-stack developer

Java - Spring MVC - PL/SQL - iBATIS - HTML - CSS - JavaScript -

REST - SOAP - JUnit - Maven - CVS

Mar. 2017 - May. 2018

ALERCE INFORMÁTICA APLICADA - Full-stack developer Java - Struts - PL/SQL - HTML - CSS - JavaScript - Maven - SVN

Jul. 2016 - Mar. 2017

GFT GROUP - Back-end developer

Java - Struts - PL/SQL - Maven - Plastic SCM

Apr. 2016 - Jul. 2016

ALTIN SOLUTIONS - Junior developer

BI with INFOR tools - OLAP cube

SKILLS

IAVA

SPRING MVC

ORACLE PL/SQL

MONGODB

HIBERNATE

HTML

JAVASCRIPT

BOOTSTRAP

LINKS

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabrielruizmunoz/



https://gabrielrmunoz.github.io/AboutMe/